import { QuizFormat } from "../../type/index.ts";

export const quizData1: QuizFormat = {
  label: "高校英語 中級",
  body: [
    {
      question: "Civil",
      choices: ["自然の", "敵対的な", "市民の", "古代の"],
      answer: "市民の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Visible",
      choices: ["隠れる", "感じる", "見える", "聞こえる"],
      answer: "見える",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Alternative",
      choices: ["伝統的な", "二次的な", "主要な", "代替の"],
      answer: "代替の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Intense",
      choices: ["平凡な", "速い", "穏やかな", "激しい"],
      answer: "激しい",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Reverse",
      choices: ["一致する", "前進する", "逆の", "同じ"],
      answer: "逆の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Economic",
      choices: ["身体的な", "文化的な", "精神的な", "経済的な"],
      answer: "経済的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Scary",
      choices: ["冷たい", "暖かい", "楽しい", "怖い"],
      answer: "怖い",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Immediate",
      choices: ["間接的な", "即時の", "長期的な", "遅延した"],
      answer: "即時の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Minute",
      choices: ["緊急の", "一般的な", "微小な", "巨大な"],
      answer: "微小な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Due",
      choices: ["適切な", "支払われるべき", "余分な", "無関係の"],
      answer: "支払われるべき",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Social",
      choices: ["秘密の", "社会的な", "個人的な", "自然の"],
      answer: "社会的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Financial",
      choices: ["情緒的な", "教育的な", "健康的な", "財政的な"],
      answer: "財政的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Wealthy",
      choices: ["幸せな", "裕福な", "中間の", "貧しい"],
      answer: "裕福な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Common",
      choices: ["特別な", "固有の", "珍しい", "一般的な"],
      answer: "一般的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Inferior",
      choices: ["同等の", "劣った", "優れた", "競争的な"],
      answer: "劣った",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Entire",
      choices: ["全体の", "断片的な", "部分の", "局所的な"],
      answer: "全体の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Permanent",
      choices: ["不安定な", "変わることのない", "一時的な", "永久の"],
      answer: "永久の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Minor",
      choices: ["二次的な", "大きい", "小さい", "主要な"],
      answer: "小さい",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Major",
      choices: ["一般的な", "主要な", "無関係な", "二次的な"],
      answer: "主要な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Obscure",
      choices: ["人気のある", "不明瞭な", "明確な", "一般的な"],
      answer: "不明瞭な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Threat",
      choices: ["保証", "友情", "脅威", "機会"],
      answer: "脅威",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Virtue",
      choices: ["無関心", "怒り", "美徳", "欠点"],
      answer: "美徳",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Tension",
      choices: ["幸福", "緊張", "リラックス", "人間"],
      answer: "緊張",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Gratitude",
      choices: ["恐怖", "嫌悪", "無関心", "感謝"],
      answer: "感謝",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Violence",
      choices: ["協力", "暴力", "平和", "喜び"],
      answer: "暴力",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Issue",
      choices: ["機会", "質問", "解決", "問題"],
      answer: "問題",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Delight",
      choices: ["怒り", "喜び", "悲しみ", "戦争"],
      answer: "喜び",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Viewpoint",
      choices: ["反対", "無関心", "同意", "視点"],
      answer: "視点",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Protest",
      choices: ["支持", "賛成", "抗議", "無関心"],
      answer: "抗議",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Grief",
      choices: ["驚き", "喜び", "心配", "悲しみ"],
      answer: "悲しみ",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Scent",
      choices: ["色", "味", "音", "香り"],
      answer: "香り",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Responsibility",
      choices: ["依存", "自由", "責任", "無責任"],
      answer: "責任",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Education",
      choices: ["休息", "遊び", "教育", "仕事"],
      answer: "教育",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Forecast",
      choices: ["現在", "歴史", "予報", "過去"],
      answer: "予報",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Sensation",
      choices: ["感情", "無感覚", "感覚", "割り箸"],
      answer: "感覚",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Sympathy",
      choices: ["反感", "同情", "喜び", "小説"],
      answer: "同情",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Shame",
      choices: ["喜び", "誇り", "無関心", "恥"],
      answer: "恥",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Impulse",
      choices: ["思考", "衝動", "計画", "反射"],
      answer: "衝動",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Instinct",
      choices: ["無関心", "学習", "知識", "本能"],
      answer: "本能",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Impact",
      choices: ["同意", "影響", "反対", "無関係"],
      answer: "影響",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Criticize",
      choices: ["褒める", "賛成する", "批判する", "疑問視する"],
      answer: "批判する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Agree",
      choices: ["反対する", "疑問を抱く", "同意する", "無関心"],
      answer: "同意する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Hesitate",
      choices: ["急ぐ", "確信する", "躊躇する", "同意する"],
      answer: "躊躇する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Amuse",
      choices: ["退屈させる", "楽しませる", "怒らせる", "混乱させる"],
      answer: "楽しませる",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Disturb",
      choices: ["邪魔する", "安心させる", "支援する", "確認する"],
      answer: "邪魔する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Confuse",
      choices: ["混乱させる", "明確にする", "強化する", "安定させる"],
      answer: "混乱させる",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Fascinate",
      choices: ["退屈させる", "怖がらせる", "魅了する", "驚かせる"],
      answer: "魅了する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Suspect",
      choices: ["信じる", "否定する", "疑う", "承認する"],
      answer: "疑う",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Praise",
      choices: ["批判する", "褒める", "分析する", "無視する"],
      answer: "褒める",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Realize",
      choices: ["夢見る", "実現する", "忘れる", "食べる"],
      answer: "実現する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Reject",
      choices: ["受け入れる", "眠る", "考慮する", "拒絶する"],
      answer: "拒絶する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Celebrate",
      choices: ["悲しむ", "祝う", "批判する", "無視する"],
      answer: "祝う",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Blame",
      choices: ["褒める", "非難する", "分析する", "掴む"],
      answer: "非難する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Suppose",
      choices: ["確認する", "退く", "疑う", "仮定する"],
      answer: "仮定する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Fade",
      choices: ["強くなる", "薄れる", "続く", "無視する"],
      answer: "薄れる",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Attract",
      choices: ["遠ざける", "引き付ける", "怒らせる", "無視する"],
      answer: "引き付ける",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Guess",
      choices: ["確認する", "心配する", "知る", "推測する"],
      answer: "推測する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Approve",
      choices: ["拒否する", "承認する", "疑う", "叩く"],
      answer: "承認する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Cherish",
      choices: ["軽視する", "大切にする", "忘れる", "選ぶ"],
      answer: "大切にする",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Astonish",
      choices: ["驚かせる", "安心させる", "無視する", "悲しませる"],
      answer: "驚かせる",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Resolve",
      choices: ["消化する", "解決する", "複雑にする", "拒否する"],
      answer: "解決する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Operate",
      choices: ["操作する", "壊す", "停止する", "認める"],
      answer: "操作する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Allow",
      choices: ["許可する", "禁止する", "飲む", "強制する"],
      answer: "許可する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Suspend",
      choices: ["続ける", "中止する", "開始する", "認識する"],
      answer: "中止する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Overlook",
      choices: ["見過ごす", "注目する", "評価する", "負ける"],
      answer: "見過ごす",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Achieve",
      choices: ["失敗する", "達成する", "諦める", "握る"],
      answer: "達成する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Direct",
      choices: ["間接的な", "直接的な", "無関係な", "間違った"],
      answer: "直接的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Handle",
      choices: ["放棄する", "取り扱う", "無視する", "壊す"],
      answer: "取り扱う",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Forbid",
      choices: ["許可する", "禁止する", "求める", "強制する"],
      answer: "禁止する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Forgive",
      choices: ["許す", "罰する", "忘れる", "飛ぶ"],
      answer: "許す",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Omit",
      choices: ["含む", "省略する", "強調する", "掛ける"],
      answer: "省略する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Quit",
      choices: ["続ける", "辞める", "開始する", "無視する"],
      answer: "辞める",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Acquire",
      choices: ["手に入れる", "失う", "避ける", "拒否する"],
      answer: "手に入れる",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Occupy",
      choices: ["占める", "空ける", "貯める", "壊す"],
      answer: "占める",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Force",
      choices: ["強制する", "許可する", "受け入れる", "説得する"],
      answer: "強制する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Require",
      choices: ["必要とする", "悩む", "持っている", "拒否する"],
      answer: "必要とする",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Deserve",
      choices: ["受けるに値する", "拒否する", "陥る", "失う"],
      answer: "受けるに値する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Retire",
      choices: ["退職する", "続ける", "始める", "響く"],
      answer: "退職する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Persuade",
      choices: ["説得する", "強制する", "受信する", "反対する"],
      answer: "説得する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Claim",
      choices: ["主張する", "拒否する", "喜ぶ", "確認する"],
      answer: "主張する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Absolute",
      choices: ["絶対的な", "相対的な", "悩んだ", "一時的な"],
      answer: "絶対的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Former",
      choices: ["以前の", "現在の", "未来の", "這う"],
      answer: "以前の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Latter",
      choices: ["後者の", "前者の", "無関係な", "悩む"],
      answer: "後者の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Responsible",
      choices: ["責任がある", "無責任な", "無関係な", "無視する"],
      answer: "責任がある",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Actual",
      choices: ["実際の", "想像の", "無関係な", "理想的な"],
      answer: "実際の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Correct",
      choices: ["正しい", "間違った", "無関係な", "不完全な"],
      answer: "正しい",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Approximate",
      choices: ["おおよその", "正確な", "無関係な", "完全な"],
      answer: "おおよその",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Following",
      choices: ["次の", "前の", "無関係な", "同時の"],
      answer: "次の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Initial",
      choices: ["初期の", "最終の", "三度目の", "途中の"],
      answer: "初期の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Ultimate",
      choices: ["最終の", "初期の", "一時的な", "増える"],
      answer: "最終の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },

    {
      question: "Plain",
      choices: ["複雑な", "明白な", "装飾的な", "抽象的な"],
      answer: "明白な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Tight",
      choices: ["緩い", "厳しい", "柔らかい", "広い"],
      answer: "厳しい",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Complete",
      choices: ["部分的な", "完全な", "未完成の", "基本的な"],
      answer: "完全な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Steady",
      choices: ["不安定な", "急速な", "変動的な", "安定した"],
      answer: "安定した",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Political",
      choices: ["政治的な", "経済的な", "個人的な", "宗教的な"],
      answer: "政治的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Temporary",
      choices: ["恒久的な", "短期的な", "定期的な", "無期限の"],
      answer: "短期的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Considerable",
      choices: ["微小な", "重要な", "無視できる", "平均的な"],
      answer: "重要な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Principal",
      choices: ["副次的な", "主要な", "無関係な", "一時的な"],
      answer: "主要な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Specific",
      choices: ["曖昧な", "特定の", "一般的な", "無関係な"],
      answer: "特定の",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Concrete",
      choices: ["具体的な", "抽象的な", "理論的な", "間接的な"],
      answer: "具体的な",
      partOfSpeech: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Legend",
      choices: ["事実", "伝説", "現実", "噂"],
      answer: "伝説",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Profit",
      choices: ["損失", "利益", "投資", "コスト"],
      answer: "利益",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Destination",
      choices: ["出発点", "目的地", "経路", "過程"],
      answer: "目的地",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Fare",
      choices: ["無料", "運賃", "割引", "手数料"],
      answer: "運賃",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Origin",
      choices: ["目的", "起源", "結果", "進行"],
      answer: "起源",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },

    {
      question: "District",
      choices: ["地区", "国", "都市", "建物"],
      answer: "地区",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Slave",
      choices: ["奴隷", "主人", "労働者", "自由人"],
      answer: "奴隷",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Treasure",
      choices: ["宝物", "廃棄物", "負債", "平凡"],
      answer: "宝物",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Mankind",
      choices: ["動物", "人類", "機械", "自然"],
      answer: "人類",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Term",
      choices: ["条件", "期間", "解決", "契約"],
      answer: "期間",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Atmosphere",
      choices: ["大気", "海洋", "土地", "宇宙"],
      answer: "大気",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Immigrant",
      choices: ["観光客", "移民", "市民", "難民"],
      answer: "移民",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Boundary",
      choices: ["中心", "境界", "接点", "距離"],
      answer: "境界",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Evolution",
      choices: ["進化", "退化", "停滞", "変化"],
      answer: "進化",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Biography",
      choices: ["伝記", "小説", "詩", "レポート"],
      answer: "伝記",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Nationality",
      choices: ["性格", "国籍", "職業", "年齢"],
      answer: "国籍",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Source",
      choices: ["結果", "源", "目的", "方法"],
      answer: "源",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Colony",
      choices: ["帝国", "都市", "植民地", "共和国"],
      answer: "植民地",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Media",
      choices: ["媒体", "文学", "技術", "政府"],
      answer: "媒体",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Destiny",
      choices: ["選択", "運命", "偶然", "計画"],
      answer: "運命",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Heritage",
      choices: ["遺産", "負債", "贈り物", "借金"],
      answer: "遺産",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Climate",
      choices: ["気候", "地形", "文化", "経済"],
      answer: "気候",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Transportation",
      choices: ["通信", "交通", "教育", "娯楽"],
      answer: "交通",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Prosperity",
      choices: ["貧困", "繁栄", "不安", "平和"],
      answer: "繁栄",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Citizen",
      choices: ["外国人", "市民", "観光客", "指導者"],
      answer: "市民",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Province",
      choices: ["都市", "国", "州", "村"],
      answer: "州",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Peninsula",
      choices: ["島", "半島", "大陸", "山脈"],
      answer: "半島",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Pavement",
      choices: ["建物", "道路", "橋", "公園"],
      answer: "道路",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Ancestor",
      choices: ["子孫", "先祖", "友人", "敵"],
      answer: "先祖",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Descendant",
      choices: ["祖先", "子孫", "減少", "認識"],
      answer: "子孫",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },

    {
      question: "Voyage",
      choices: ["旅行", "滞在", "探求", "停滞"],
      answer: "旅行",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Outlook",
      choices: ["展望", "内観", "過去", "予測"],
      answer: "展望",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Occupation",
      choices: ["趣味", "職業", "休息", "教育"],
      answer: "職業",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Tradition",
      choices: ["革新", "伝統", "変化", "現代性"],
      answer: "伝統",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Civilization",
      choices: ["野蛮", "文明", "自然", "単純さ"],
      answer: "文明",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Progress",
      choices: ["後退", "進歩", "停滞", "減少"],
      answer: "進歩",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Decade",
      choices: ["世紀", "年", "月", "十年"],
      answer: "十年",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Era",
      choices: ["瞬間", "時代", "日", "週"],
      answer: "時代",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Congress",
      choices: ["会社", "議会", "集会", "団体"],
      answer: "議会",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Tribe",
      choices: ["国家", "部族", "集団", "家族"],
      answer: "部族",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Afford",
      choices: ["拒否する", "提供する", "要求する", "節約する"],
      answer: "提供する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Assume",
      choices: ["確認する", "想定する", "拒否する", "調査する"],
      answer: "想定する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Approach",
      choices: ["離れる", "接近する", "避ける", "認める"],
      answer: "接近する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Found",
      choices: ["創設する", "破壊する", "失う", "放棄する"],
      answer: "創設する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Separate",
      choices: ["結合する", "分離する", "混合する", "一致する"],
      answer: "分離する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Translate",
      choices: ["無視する", "翻訳する", "削除する", "保存する"],
      answer: "翻訳する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Declare",
      choices: ["隠す", "宣言する", "拒否する", "疑問を抱く"],
      answer: "宣言する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Ruin",
      choices: ["改善する", "破壊する", "構築する", "修復する"],
      answer: "破壊する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Remain",
      choices: ["去る", "残る", "変化する", "進化する"],
      answer: "残る",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Appear",
      choices: ["消える", "現れる", "隠れる", "変わる"],
      answer: "現れる",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Exchange",
      choices: ["保持する", "交換する", "拒否する", "単独で行う"],
      answer: "交換する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Organize",
      choices: ["混乱させる", "組織する", "破壊する", "削減する"],
      answer: "組織する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Excel",
      choices: ["失敗する", "優れる", "平均的である", "後退する"],
      answer: "優れる",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Decrease",
      choices: ["増加する", "減少する", "安定する", "変化しない"],
      answer: "減少する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Conduct",
      choices: ["貯める", "実施する", "拒否する", "中止する"],
      answer: "実施する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Develop",
      choices: ["後退する", "発展する", "停止する", "減少する"],
      answer: "発展する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Invade",
      choices: ["退却する", "侵略する", "保護する", "飲む"],
      answer: "侵略する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Delay",
      choices: ["急ぐ", "遅延する", "叩く", "前進する"],
      answer: "遅延する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Ban",
      choices: ["許可する", "禁止する", "奨励する", "受信する"],
      answer: "禁止する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Bet",
      choices: ["保証する", "賭ける", "拒否する", "読む"],
      answer: "賭ける",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Cease",
      choices: ["続ける", "停止する", "開始する", "加速する"],
      answer: "停止する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Adjust",
      choices: ["呼ぶ", "調整する", "破壊する", "拒否する"],
      answer: "調整する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Undergo",
      choices: ["避ける", "経験する", "回る", "拒否する"],
      answer: "経験する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Conquer",
      choices: ["敗北する", "征服する", "逃げる", "協力する"],
      answer: "征服する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Advance",
      choices: ["後退する", "進む", "停止する", "聞く"],
      answer: "進む",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Submit",
      choices: ["拒否する", "提出する", "隠す", "溶ける"],
      answer: "提出する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Transfer",
      choices: ["保持する", "転送する", "拒否する", "破棄する"],
      answer: "転送する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Unite",
      choices: ["分離する", "統合する", "競争する", "座る"],
      answer: "統合する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Release",
      choices: ["保持する", "放出する", "拒否する", "抑制する"],
      answer: "放出する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Participate",
      choices: ["避ける", "参加する", "消える", "観察する"],
      answer: "参加する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Raise",
      choices: ["下げる", "上げる", "維持する", "食べる"],
      answer: "上げる",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Trace",
      choices: ["要求する", "追跡する", "放棄する", "拒否する"],
      answer: "追跡する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Cancel",
      choices: ["確認する", "キャンセルする", "進める", "放置する"],
      answer: "キャンセルする",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Rule",
      choices: ["従う", "支配する", "拒否する", "用意する"],
      answer: "支配する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Disappear",
      choices: ["現れる", "消える", "変化する", "停止する"],
      answer: "消える",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Manage",
      choices: ["無視する", "管理する", "放棄する", "破壊する"],
      answer: "管理する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Surround",
      choices: ["避ける", "取り囲む", "分離する", "結合する"],
      answer: "取り囲む",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Intend",
      choices: ["意図する", "無視する", "拒否する", "忘れる"],
      answer: "意図する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Reserve",
      choices: ["解放する", "予約する", "拒否する", "破棄する"],
      answer: "予約する",
      partOfSpeech: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Cost",
      choices: ["利益", "価格", "損失", "報酬"],
      answer: "価格",
      partOfSpeech: 1,
    },
  ],
};
